pagemodo.com 2018-04-22

# Pagemodo.com - Privacy

## Privacy Policy

Pagemodo is a suite of custom Facebook Page creation solutions (collectively "Pagemodo" or "Services"). Your privacy and protection of information you share with us while using our Services is very important to us.

This "Privacy Policy" explains what information we gather from our users and how we use it. By using or accessing our Services, you are accepting the practices described in this Privacy Policy. (Capitalized terms not defined herein have the meaning set forth in our Terms of Service).

Pagemodo is not intended for children under 13 years of age. Consistent with the Federal Children's Online Privacy Protection Act of 1998 ("COPPA"), we will never knowingly gather or use personally identifiable information from anyone under the age of 13, and we do not allow anyone under the age of 13 to register on Pagemodo.

### What information does Pagemodo gather?

Pagemodo gathers and stores three types of information about users that are subject to our Privacy Policy:

  1. Information users provide to us: These are voluntary submissions made when creating an account on Pagemodo or through your use of the Services, such as name and email address, or payment information provided during purchases. Please understand that when you sign into Pagemodo or post or upload any content, your information is not anonymous to us.
  2. Information we collect when users interact with Pagemodo: We keep track of user interactions with our Services, such as visiting a web page, clicking a button, and choosing a form. Also, when users access our Services, we may collect information about their access method (such as hardware and software attributes), location, IP address, and pages they visit. In addition, we store certain information from their browser using "cookies". (For more on cookies, please see the section "What are cookies?")
  3. Information we receive from third parties: We do not own or operate any third-party services offered that you may use or interact with through our Services (collectively, "Third Party Services"). Whenever you visit, use or interact with a Third Party Service, we may receive information from them, including information about actions you take and Content you post on that service.

### Why does Pagemodo gather information about me?

Pagemodo collects information in order to improve the content and quality of our Services and to provide a customized experience tailored to your needs. Any personally identifiable information we collect (including email addresses, physical addresses or phone numbers) is not shared with or sold to other organizations for commercial purposes, except to provide products or services you've requested, when we have your permission, or under special circumstances outlined in this Privacy Policy.

### What are cookies?

Pagemodo may place a text file called a "cookie" in the browser files of your computer. These cookies help us make Pagemodo easier to use, to make our advertising better, and to protect both you and Pagemodo. For example, a cookie may be used to store or "remember" your Member login information (but not your password) so that you are not required to manually log into the site at every visit. You can remove or block cookies using the settings in your browser, but in some cases that may impact your ability to use some of our Services.

Our advertisers and partners may also set cookies through our Services. For more information, please see the section "What about third party advertisers and links?"

### What about third party advertisers and links?

In the course of serving advertisements on Pagemodo, a third-party advertiser may place or recognize a unique cookie on your browser. Additionally, some links from Pagemodo may lead to websites operated by other companies. While these websites and advertisements may be co-branded with our name or logo, they are not operated or maintained by us. We do not control these cookies and users of Pagemodo Services should check the privacy policy of the relevant advertiser to understand whether and how it uses cookies. Pagemodo is not responsible for websites operated by third parties that are linked to by any of our sites.

Ads appearing on the Services may be delivered to you by Google Ad Manager, DoubleClick, or other advertising partners. Information about your visits to this site, such as the number of times you have viewed an ad (but not your name, address or other personal information), is used to serve ads to you. For more information about these partners, their cookies, and how to "opt-out," please follow the links below.

  * Network Advertising Initiative (NAI)
  * Google Ad Manager
  * DoubleClick

### How secure is my information?

Pagemodo uses commercially reasonable physical, electronic, and procedural measures to safeguard any information in our possession against loss, theft and unauthorized use, disclosure or modification. We limit access to personal information about you to employees whom we believe reasonably need that information to provide support, products, or services to you or to fulfill their roles within our organization.

Although we have established and maintain security procedures to protect your personally identifiable information, please be aware that no security measures are perfect or impenetrable. You can reduce the risk of unauthorized access to your information by using common sense security practices such as choosing a strong password, using different passwords for different services, and using up-to-date antivirus software.

Please report any security violations to us on this automated form.

### What control do I have over my information?

As a registered Member, you may modify or update your personal account information at any time by logging into your account. Should you desire to do so, you may also delete and close your Pagemodo account at any time by contacting oursupport team. Note that removed or deleted information may persist in backup copies for a reasonable period of time.

### How is information shared?

Pagemodo will not share your personally identifiable information with others except as described herein and in limited circumstances where we believe such sharing is reasonably necessary to offer the Services, legally required, or permitted by you. For example, we may provide information to service providers to help us bring you the services we offer. Specifically, we may use third parties to facilitate our business, such as to host the Services at a co-location facility for servers, to send out email updates about the Services, to remove repetitive information from our user lists, to process payments for products or services, or to provide search results or links (including sponsored links). In connection with these offerings and business operations, our service providers may have access to your personal information for use for a limited time.

Where we utilize third parties for the processing of any personal information, we implement reasonable contractual and technical protections limiting the use of that information to the Pagemodo-specified purposes. We may store personal information in locations outside the direct control of Pagemodo (for instance, on servers or databases co-located with hosting providers).

Except as otherwise described in this Privacy Policy, we will not disclose personal information to any third party unless we believe that disclosure is necessary: (1) to conform to legal requirements or to respond to a subpoena, search warrant or other legal process received by Pagemodo, whether or not a response is required by applicable law; (2) to enforce the Pagemodo Terms of Service or to protect our rights; or (3) to protect the safety or rights of members of the public or users of the Services. Pagemodo reserves the right to transfer personal information to a successor in interest that acquires rights to that information as a result of the sale of Pagemodo or substantially all of its assets to that successor in interest. We may also transfer such information in the course of corporate divestitures, mergers, or dissolution.

### How am I notified of changes to this Privacy Policy

We may change this Privacy Policy pursuant to the procedures outlined in our Terms of Service. Unless stated otherwise, our current Privacy Policy applies to all information we have about you and your account. If we make changes to this Privacy Policy we will notify you by publication here.

### Who can I contact about this Privacy Policy?

To submit an inquiry about our Privacy Policy, please contact our support department.
